she is nice the Cavalry's here
that's my line I think I could have a
look at one of those bombs of yours over
my dead body
I get cold just looking at you yeah you
should look somewhere else
you're just a no-good bully how can you
even look at yourself in the mirror I
beg your pardon I consider myself a
freedom fighter a misunderstood one you
are terrible that's cold
I hate bullies like you that's cold
you I believe agile Pigface a man they
told me the other day
all right I'll try not to get us killed
out there
mm-hmm shut up you hokum you know I
never would have taken you for someone
with such a homely home the Queen sure
seems to have an interest in me spy she
fancies me I hate to break her heart
remember that time we stole the crown
jewels all hail King Jameson Fox the
first and Duke try and steer a single
forewarns obey on me best behavior where
did you hide your treasure you could
hardly have it on your person don't
suppose you'd like to tried this I mean
I don't think you could handle it and I
thought I'd taken my licks I was a
reckless youth for you are something
else entirely
bots dime a dozen actually if they spend
most of her
Foundation grants on me it was not
inexpensive you look like the kind of
guy he could use something blown up a
candidate just came to mind I admire the
way you deal with those butts wanna team
up not if you were the last human on
earth I heard there's a nice reward for
bringing you fellas in maybe we good
mm-hmm
well something out night